{
"question": "弱い",
"answer": "よわい"
},
{
"question": "牛乳",
"answer": "ぎゅうにゅう"
},
{
"question": "三",
"answer": "さん"
},
{
"question": "大丈夫",
"answer": "だいじょうぶ"
},
{
"question": "黒い",
"answer": "くろい"
},
{
"question": "皆さん",
"answer": "みなさん"
},
{
"question": "半分",
"answer": "はんぶん"
},
{
"question": "押す",
"answer": "おす"
},
{
"question": "勤める",
"answer": "つとめる"
},
{
"question": "熱い",
"answer": "あつい"
},
{
"question": "三つ",
"answer": "みっつ"
},
{
"question": "果物",
"answer": "くだもの"
},
{
"question": "今週",
"answer": "こんしゅう"
},
{
"question": "右",
"answer": "みぎ"
},
{
"question": "甘い",
"answer": "あまい"
},
{
"question": "晩",
"answer": "ばん"
},
{
"question": "幾つ",
"answer": "いくつ"
},
{
"question": "階段",
"answer": "かいだん"
},
{
"question": "大勢",
"answer": "おおぜい"
},
{
"question": "張る",
"answer": "はる"
},
